{
    "fourAnswerQuestions": [
        {
            "question": "The official words of House Lannister are",
            "answers": [
                "Hear Me Roar",
                "A Lannister Always Pays Their Debts",
                "Lannisters don't act like fools",
                "Lannisters shits gold"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "questions": "Tyreek Hill is nicknamed",
            "answers": [
                "The bolt",
                "Cheetah",
                "The Blur",
                "Zoom"

            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the fastest animal",
            "answers": [
                "Turtle",
                "Cheetah",
                "Walrus",
                "Pig"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7 - 8?",
            "answers": [
                "1",
                "4",
                "-2",
                "-1"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Trailer Park Boys is filmed in...'",
            "answers": [
                "England",
                "Ghana",
                "United States",
                "Canada"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "In Sam Rami's Spiderman. The public identity of Spiderman is",
            "answers": [
                "Norman Osborn",
                "Gwen Stacy",
                "Peter Parker",
                "Miles Morales "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
            "questions": "Steve Irwin is famously known as",
            "answers": [
                "The Alligator Hunter",
                "Gator's Gat",
                "The Crocodile Hunter",
                "The Australian Annihilator"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "As of March 1, 2023, Toronto's current mayor is",
            "answers": [
                "Gil Penalosa",
                "John Tory",
                "Jennifer Keesmaat",
                "Jennifer McKelvie"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 4
        }

    ],
    "trueFalseQuestions": [
        {
            "question": "A Hotdog is a sandwich",
            "answers": [
                "yes",
                "no"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ketchup is a condiment",
            "answers": [
                "yes",
                "no"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the opposite of north",
            "answers": [
                "north",
                "south"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Canadians drive on the right side of the road",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Australia is a continent",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        { 
            "question": "Johnny Depp portrays Grindewald in Fantastic Beasts 3",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Toronto has an NBA team",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"

            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Toronto has a WNBA team",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },

        {
          
        }
    ],
    "questionType": [
        "fourAnswerQuestions",
        "trueFalseQuestions"
    ],
    "score": [
        {
            "name": "test",
            "score": 1
        }
    ]
}